[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(null.runtimeType);",
    "answers": ["null", "dynamic", "Object", "Null"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(0.1 + 0.2 == 0.3);",
    "answers": ["true", "false"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following methods converts a JSON object to a string?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["jsonDecode()", "jsonEncode()", "toString()", "jsonStringify()"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What does the 'this' keyword refer to in a Dart class?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["The global object", "The object that called the function", "The current instance of the class", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "How do you write a comment in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["<!-- This is a comment -->", "// This is a comment", "/* This is a comment */", "# This is a comment"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print([] + []);",
    "answers": ["[]", "null", "undefined", "[]"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a Dart data type?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["bool", "Null", "dynamic", "Float"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Which of the following methods is used to add elements to a list?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["add()", "push()", "append()", "insert()"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(double.nan.runtimeType);",
    "answers": ["num", "double", "NaN", "null"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Which company developed Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["Microsoft", "Apple", "Netscape", "Google"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Which method can be used to create a new list from an existing list?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["sublist()", "splice()", "split()", "reduce()"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to stop a periodic timer in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["cancel()", "clearTimeout()", "stopTimer()", "stopTimeout()"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "Which of the following is used to define a variable in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["var", "let", "final", "All of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(1 == '1');",
    "answers": ["true", "false"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(1 === '1');",
    "answers": ["true", "false"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "What is the correct syntax for importing a Dart library?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["import 'library.dart';", "#include 'library.dart'", "<import 'library.dart'>", "library 'library.dart'"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a reserved word in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["interface", "throws", "program", "short"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "How do you declare a Dart variable?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["variable carName;", "var carName;", "let carName;", "declare carName;"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(0 == '');",
    "answers": ["true", "false"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(0 === '');",
    "answers": ["true", "false"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "What is the purpose of the 'debugger' statement in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["It stops the execution of Dart code", "It triggers a breakpoint in the code", "It logs a message to the console", "It catches errors in the code"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print([] == []);",
    "answers": ["true", "false"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "What does 'NaN' stand for in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["Not a Null", "Number and Null", "Not a Number", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print([1, 2, 3] + [4, 5, 6]);",
    "answers": ["[1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6]", "[1, 2, 3][4, 5, 6]", "1,2,34,5,6", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "What is the correct way to check if a variable 'x' is not equal to '5'?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["x <> 5", "x =! 5", "x != 5", "x !== 5"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "What is the output of the following code?",
    "code": "print('5' + 3);",
    "answers": ["8", "53", "Error", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "Which function is used to parse a string to an integer in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["int.parse()", "double.parse()", "num.parse()", "Integer()"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Which of the following is a ternary operator in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["?", ":", "??", "&&"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(true + false);",
    "answers": ["truefalse", "1", "NaN", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Which method is used to round a number to its nearest integer in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["round()", "ceil()", "floor()", "truncate()"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print((() {}).runtimeType);",
    "answers": ["Object", "Function", "dynamic", "String"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "Which method can be used to join all elements of a list into a string?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["concat()", "join()", "push()", "pop()"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print('Hello'.codeUnitAt(0));",
    "answers": ["H", "e", "o", "72"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "What is the output of the following code?",
    "code": "print(bool.fromEnvironment(''));",
    "answers": ["true", "false", "undefined", "null"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "Which method is used to convert a string to lowercase letters in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["toLowerCase()", "toLower()", "changeCase(lower)", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(2 + '2' - '2');",
    "answers": ["20", "2", "NaN", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "Which method can be used to extract a section of a string in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["substring()", "split()", "replace()", "search()"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(1 / 0);",
    "answers": ["NaN", "Infinity", "undefined", "Error"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "What does the 'isNaN' function do?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["Checks if a value is a number", "Checks if a value is not a number", "Checks if a value is null", "Checks if a value is undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "What is the purpose of the 'break' statement in a loop?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["To pause the loop", "To stop the loop and exit", "To restart the loop", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "Which method can be used to convert a string to an array?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["split()", "join()", "toList()", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "What is the output of the following code?",
    "code": "print(bool.fromEnvironment('0'));",
    "answers": ["true", "false", "undefined", "null"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print([].runtimeType);",
    "answers": ["Object", "List", "Array", "dynamic"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "Which method can be used to remove the last element from a list?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["removeLast()", "remove()", "removeAt()", "removeRange()"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(int.parse('10') - 5);",
    "answers": ["105", "5", "NaN", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "What does the 'map' method do in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["Maps one list to another list", "Creates a new list with the results of calling a provided function on every element in the calling list", "Filters elements from a list", "None of the above"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "What will the following code output?",
    "code": "print(2 * null);",
    "answers": ["0", "null", "NaN", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "Which statement is used to declare a constant in Dart?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["constant", "let", "const", "var"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "What is the output of the following code?",
    "code": "print(int.parse('10') * 2);",
    "answers": ["20", "102", "NaN", "undefined"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "Which method can be used to add one or more elements to the beginning of a list?",
    "code": "",
    "answers": ["insertAll(0, [])", "insert(0, element)", "push()", "unshift()"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }
]
